The Original Classic
Dark Night of the Scarecrow is a horror, tv movie
film directed by Frank De Felitta.
Bubba, an intellectually disabled man, is falsely
accused of attacking a young girl.
Disguised as a scarecrow, he hides in a cornfield, only to be
hunted down and shot by four vigilante men.
After they are acquitted due to lack of evidence, the men
find themselves being stalked one by one.
Otis P. Hazelrigg, played by Charles Durning.
Bubba Ritter, played by Larry Drake.
Skeeter Norris, played by Robert F. Lyons.
Philby, played by Claude Earl Jones.
Harless Hocker, played by Lane Smith.
Marylee Williams, played by Tonya Crowe.
Dark Night of the Scarecrow is a 1981 American made-for-television horror film directed by
veteran novelist Frank De Felitta (author of Audrey Rose) from a script by J.D.
Feigelson's intent had been to make an independent feature, but his script was bought by CBS for
television; despite this, only minor changes were made to the original teleplay.
The film explores themes of mentally disabled,
grave, scarecrow, cover-up, revenge.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.